{
    "id": "b3e987f4a1c6453eb906ba7e7c52a27d",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Delhi is …………….. than Mumbai.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hot",
                "hotter",
                "hottest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45116f4d01364710ba602c881d17bc28"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….. youngest brother serves in the army.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "My",
                "Me",
                "Mine"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee47eae4bbe64b0c9ad8bcce61d870bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had ………………. most interesting experience during the picnic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afca3d78e40b4645b5168fcd8c7f9225"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mr. Ramesh is ……………….. most popular lecturer in our college.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f2ec0a6fa1bb4d7d8631e95ea4de58b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am satisfied only with ………………… best.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7240391e236a468887ccb52ffaffe0d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kodaikanal is one of the ……………… hill stations in South India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lovely",
                "lovelier",
                "loveliest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4781d46463ed4892bb7f997ec9afdc8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………… of the two brothers is getting married next month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "younger",
                "youngest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bbcb38810ab14cbf810005968479d9c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………….. most useful book on the subject.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aac291fefcaf4069b04974b1bd9b8359"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have not seen ………………… better film than this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d9b4f7667e1e4e139a426c29a593ee6a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only the ………………. member can be elected the President.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "older",
                "oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c26b0a59bb2b423ea3afeb22679d5784"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………….. worst accident in recent times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f5219391ff7444a38e26b540202e185e"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. Charles seemed to be covered with hair.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most of",
                "The most of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6a5d00d7b39e4137a3a89a713dc7fed3"
        }
    ]
}